(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-06T22:38:39.300104",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ここは、ねぽらぼ学園！
This is Nepolabo Academy!
部活もクラスも違うけど、ねねたち、同じ学生寮に住んでるんだ！
Our club activities and classes are different, but we live in the same dorm!
ふざけて、笑って、時々喧嘩して！でも、集まると、なんか落ち着く！
Fooling around, laughing, and sometimes fighting! But when we gather, we somehow feel at ease!
今日も談話室は賑やか。誰かの声が聞こえるだけで、安心するんだよね。
Today the common room is lively again. Just hearing someone's voice makes me feel relieved.
この場所で、私たちだけの学寮生活を作るなんて、楽しそうでワクワクする！
Making our own student dorm life in this place sounds fun and exciting!
さあ！
Come on!
私たちの！
Our...
輝く青春が！
...shining youth...
始まる！
...begins!
ねぽらぼ学園！
Nepolabo Academy!
5周年記念！！輝く学寮祭！
5th Anniversary!! Shining Dorm Festival!
今日は学寮祭！生徒会が中心になって開催する、夏の一大イベント！
Today is the Dorm Festival! A huge summer event hosted mainly by the student council!
会長からの頼みで、急遽ねぽらぼで出し物を考えることになったんだけどーー
At the president's request, we had to suddenly come up with a performance for Nepolabo, but...
何も考えられてなーーい！！！
We haven't thought of anything at all!!!
やばいよ...。気づいたら、もう当日だよ〜〜〜！
This is bad... before I knew it, it's already the day of the festival!
だから言ったじゃん、もっと早く集まって決めようって！
That's why I told you we should have met sooner to decide!
いや〜なんとかなるって思ってたんだけどな〜
Well, I thought we would manage somehow.
うぅ...これはまずい...。変なことやったら、会長になんて言われるか...
Ugh... this is bad... if we do something weird, what will the president say to us...
（……）
,s:
......
よしっ、断ろう！！
Alright, let's decline!
やめなー！当日に断れるわけないでしょ！
Stop that! There's no way we can decline on the day of the event!
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミちゃんならきっと許してくれるって
It's fine, it'll be fine. Lamy will surely forgive us.
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミィちゃんならきっと許してくれるって♪
It's fine, it's fine. I'm sure Lamy will forgive us.
なんでラミィだけ謝る前提なのよ！
Why is it assumed only Lamy is going to apologize?!
…いや、まだ終わってない！！
...No, it's not over yet!
学園祭はお昼から…
The school festival starts at noon...
ほんのちょっとだけ、まだ時間はある！
We still have just a little bit of time!
よし、とりあえず案を出してみよっか～
Alright, let's try coming up with some ideas first.
学校の祭りといえば…
Speaking of school festivals...
焼きそば、じゃがバター、
Yakisoba, buttered potatoes,
唐揚げ、クレープ、ポテト…
fried chicken, crepes, French fries...
食べ物しかないじゃん！！
That's all food!!
…でも今から仕込みはちょっと無理かもね
...But it might be too late to prepare ingredients now.
まあできるとしたら
Well, if we were to do something,
炎天下でカラカラな喉に染み渡る…ラミィ水！！
how about Lamy Water to quench a dry throat under the blazing sun?
これは売れるぞ～
This will definitely sell!
やめろおおお！！！
Stop it!!!
うっひょおぉ！しぼり出して～
Whoa! Squeeze it all out!
バカなこと言ってないで！もっと真面目に考えなさいって！
Don't say such stupid things! Think about this seriously!
そんなに言うならラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
Since you're so against it, what do you want to do, Lamy?
ラミィ？
Me?
そうだなぁ…やっぱり歌は歌いたいし…
Well... I do want to sing after all...
バンドとか、かな？
Maybe a band?
ふつう
How generic.
ひねりがない～
No originality.
……っフ
*chuckle*
こいつら…！
Why you...!
でもまあ、歌はいいかもね～
But singing actually sounds like a good idea.
ショート動画用にいろいろな曲練習しているし、
We've been practicing various songs for short videos,
その中から何かやってみる？
so why don't we perform one of them?
じゃあねね、あれやりたい！
Then I want to do that one!
元気いっぱいの、ねねたちにピッタリなやつ！！
The high-energy one that's perfect for us!
あ～～～、あれね！
Ah! That one!
いいんじゃない！
That sounds great!
じゃ、とりあえずやってみますか！
Alright, let's give it a try then!
キメマスター！！
Kimemaster!
前人ゼロの未踏地だよなあ
It's an uncharted land with zero pioneers.
そいやー！
Soiya!
生まれ変わる一歩目は
The first step to being reborn...
一歩目が大事さ 恐れないよ
...that first step is crucial, don't be afraid!
何度でも平気な顔で走り出して
Start running with a calm face, over and over again!
行かなきゃ！上々の気分さ
We've got to go! I'm in the best mood!
やってみたいことには欲張りだね
We're greedy when it comes to things we want to try.
欲張りごめんね 直さないよ
Sorry for being greedy, but we won't change!
何度でも未来を書き換えたくなるのさ
It makes us want to rewrite the future time and again!
行かなきゃ！最高の仲間と
We've got to go, with the best of friends!
星になろうよ
Let's become stars.
輝きたいよ
We want to shine.
今は今だけ
Now is only for now,
後悔しないようにねっ
so make sure you don't regret it!
さぁおいで monsters
Come on over, monsters!
踊れば monsters
Once we dance, we're monsters!
こんなにも無敵 Pika Stars!
We are absolutely invincible Pika Stars!
夢が kira-kira
Our dreams are sparkling,
無駄に kira-kira？？
sparkling for no reason?
前進だ doka-doka！！
Moving forward with a bang!
はわっ通りまるー！
Whoa, coming through!
キマっちゃってる！？
We've got it down!
全速モードでよいしょっしょ 制限はね無視だよ
At full speed, heave-ho! Ignore all the limits!
なにかとやっぱっぱ 全力がいいよね
Anything and everything, going all out is the best!
笑顔あり
With a smile,
キメ顔あり
with a serious face,
最強 BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来！
aim for the future with the strongest Big Bang!
チェストー！
Chest!
手と手取りあったらるんたった 怖くはないよね
Hand in hand, skip along, we're not afraid!
夢の計測メーターは振り切れそうだよ
The dream meter is about to go off the charts!
地球から
From the Earth,
やってきたボクらは
we came,
本日も go ahead! go ahead!
and today we go ahead, go ahead!
怒られるまで？
Until we get scolded?
・・・怒られても止まれないのです
...Even if we get scolded, we can't stop!
騒々しくてもごめんなさーい！
Sorry for being so loud!
先陣誰だい？ ボクらだい！
Who's leading the charge? We are!
ほいほいっ
Hoy, hoy!
いわゆる前人ゼロの未踏地だよなあ
It's an uncharted land with zero pioneers.
そいやー！
Soiya!
ゆずらないないない百歩目も
Not giving up, even on the hundredth step,
百歩ゆずるなんて負けよ駄目よ
giving in would be a defeat, no way!
ゴールへのロードは砂利と岩だらけで
The road to the goal is full of gravel and rocks,
泣いても顔は “に・や・り”
but even if we cry, we wear a smirk!
そんな時あきらめ悪く進め
At times like that, march on stubbornly!
だってほらあきらめたくない夢が
Because, you see, we have a dream we don't want to give up!
進化してみんなを果ての果ての空へ
It evolves and takes everyone to the ends of the sky!
連れ去る
Carrying away,
ボクら地球女子
we Earth girls!
憧れたんだ
We longed for it,
星の光は
the starlight
消えないときめき
is an undying heartbeat!
心拍数上がりまくりっ
My heart rate is shooting up!
さぁ跳んで monsters
Come on, jump, monsters!
暴れちゃお monsters
Let's go wild, monsters!
だいたんで不敵 Pika Stars!
We are bold and daring Pika Stars!
随時きらめきが上昇中つまり好調中
Our sparkle is rising constantly, in other words, we're doing great!
あ、サビきまーす
Oh, here comes the chorus!
たぶん勝利は、
Maybe victory is...
キマっちゃってる！
...already decided!
いいとこだったのにー！
Just when it was getting good!
バンドじゃないからせっせっせ カッコつけなければ
We're not a band, so we have to try hard to look cool!
バンドじゃないからよいよいよい カッコがつつのだよ
We're not a band, so we end up looking cool naturally!
バカ騒ぎ
Making a racket,
やんちゃ騒ぎ
raising some mischief,
やったもん勝ち狙っちゃえ未来！
first come, first served! Aim for the future!
チェストー！
Chest!
銀河のどっかの頂点に旗を立てるまで
Until we plant our flag on some peak in the galaxy!
ニューなレコードの更新は続くんだってば
The setting of new records will keep going!
地球から
From the Earth,
やってきたボクらよ
we came,
やりまくれ go ahead! go ahead!
do as you please, go ahead! go ahead!
さぁ次の星へ！
Now, onto the next star!
一歩が百歩の始まり
A single step is the start of a hundred,
だから行こうよすぐに行こうよ
so let's go, let's go right away!
無理は道理よりも強引だなー
Forcing things is more pushy than reason!
瞬間をキミと一緒にね monsters！！
Sharing this moment with you, monsters!
真っ暗な空かもしれないけどボクらは輝きたい
It might be a pitch-black sky, but we want to shine!
お目々を開いてお目々を離すなよー！？
Open your eyes and don't look away, okay?
もんすきー！
Monsukii!
モンスター！ モンスター！ モンスター！
Monster! Monster! Monster!
前人未踏の宇宙に全速の全力でgoだ yeah！！
Go into uncharted space with all our might! Yeah!
大変だい そうだそうだ
It's a big deal! That's right, that's right!
地球はブルーだブルーだっ
The Earth is blue, it's blue!
ぜんぶを欲しがれ EARTH女子！
Want it all, Earth Girls!
全快かい そうかもそうかもっ
Fully recovered? Maybe, maybe!
宇宙のスターにスターにっ
To be a star in space, a star!
なりたい なりたい
I want to be, I want to be!
なれそう？なれそうだよ！
Think we can make it? Yes we can!
キマっちゃったしね！
We totally nailed it!
全速モードでよいしょっしょ 制限は無視だよ
Full speed mode, yoishossho! Ignore the limits!
なんでもかんでもやっぱっぱ 全力がいいよね
Everything and anything, going all out is the best!
笑顔あり 涙あり
With smiles, with tears,
最強BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来！
Strongest Big Bang, aim for the future!
チェストー！
Chest!
手とりあったらるんたった 怖くはないよね
Holding hands, runtatta! It's not scary, is it?
夢の計測メーターは 振り切れそうだよ
The dream meter is about to break!
地球から
From Earth...
やってきたボクらは
...we have come...
本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
...today as well! Go ahead! Go ahead!
怒られるまで？
Until we get scolded?
怒られても 止まれないのです
Even if we get scolded, we can't stop!
最後の最後もごめんなさーい！
Even at the very end, we're sorry!
先陣誰だい？ボクらだい！
Who's at the vanguard? It's us!
いわゆる前人ゼロの未路地だよなぁ
The uncharted path of zero predecessors, so to speak!
もう一回っ
One more time!
大いなる一歩さ ボクらと最高速で
A giant leap at top speed with us!
前人ゼロの未路地へ Go!!
To the uncharted path with zero predecessors, Go!
そいやー！
Soiyaa!
よ〜し次はバンドだ！
できる曲を片っ端からやっていこ〜〜！！
Alright, next up is the band!
Let's play every song we can, one after another!
でも私たち、楽器できなくない……？
But wait, can we even play instruments...?
こういうのはね、雰囲気が大事！
頑張ってる姿を見せれば、それでOK！
It's all about the vibe! If we show them
we're trying our best, it'll be fine!
バカにしておいて結局やるのね…
You tease it, but we're actually
doing it anyway...
じゃあまず、誰が何やるか決めよう〜！
ねねはギターっ！
Then first, let's decide who plays what!
Nene is on guitar!
じゃあししろんはドラムかな〜
Then Shishiron will do drums, I guess~
ポルカはベースで〜！
Polka is on bass~!
じゃあラミィは…シンセ、やろうかなっ
Then Lamy will... do synth, I suppose.
そうしたら演出も考えないとな〜
In that case, we need to think
about the stage effects too~
派手にドカーンってしたい！！
I want to go 'kaboom' with a bang!!
ざっくりだな〜
That's pretty vague~
サビにキャノンとか出す？
Should we shoot off cannons during the chorus?
いいね！照明もレーザー出したりして
ピカピカにしていこう！
Sounds good! Let's make the lights flash
with lasers and stuff!
じゃあ、ねねはポルカと動き回って
パフォーマンスしよう！
Alright, Nene and Polka will
move around the stage and perform!
やるやるっ！任せて〜！！
I'm down! Leave it to me!!
だ、大丈夫かぁ？
間に合わなくってアタタフタするんじゃない？
Are you... sure about this? Aren't we going
to panic if we run out of time?
まぁ、それも“わたしたちらしさ”ってことで〜
Well, that chaos is also very 'us', you know~
そう！ノリでなんとかなるなる！
Exactly! We'll manage with our momentum!
あ、そうだ、バンド名、どうするの？
Oh, right, what about our band name?
えっ！かっこいいやつがいい〜！
Oh! I want a really cool one!
じゃあ、『青春★ピチピチフルスロットル団』！！
How about 'Youthful ★ Bouncing
Full Throttle Brigade'!!
だ、ださっ！？
Th-That's so uncool!?
もうちょい5期生要素も入れたいね。
ラーメン、芝刈り機、低気圧……
I'd like to add a bit more Gen 5 flavor.
Ramen, lawnmower, low pressure...
「カブトムシ」って入れたらかっこいいよ！
It'd be cool if we put 'Beetle' in it!
「青春低気圧★ラーメンピチピチフルスロットル芝刈り団」！！
'Youthful Low Pressure ★ Ramen Bouncing
Full Throttle Lawnmower Brigade'!!
混ぜるな！ぐちゃぐちゃだろっ
Don't just mash them together!
That's a total mess!
じゃあラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
Then what would you prefer, Lamy-chan?
えーっ、やっぱり可愛いのがいいかなぁ〜？
「ねぽらぼハーモニー」とか〜♪
Well, maybe something cute would be better?
Like 'NePoLaBo Harmony'...
それでいいのかラミィ
Are you really okay with that, Lamy?
かっこよくないよラミィ
That's not cool at all, Lamy.
俺、恥ずかしいよラミィ
I'm embarrassed, Lamy.
ほんっとに……お前らっ！！
Seriously... you guys!!
よ〜し！バンド名も決まったし、やってみますかー！
Alright! The band name is set, so let's do this!
これで、学園祭の注目はいただきだーっ！
With this, we'll steal the spotlight
at the school festival!
えっ！？あれでいくの！？
Wait, we're actually going with *that* name!?
いくぞーっ！よーい…
Here we go! Ready...
どん！！！
Go!!!
Ready!! Steady!! Derby!!
走って
Run!
憧れを越えて
Surpassing our dreams!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
まだ見たことのないスピードの向こう側へ
To the other side of a speed we've never seen before,
ウォームアップは完璧さ
Our warm-up is absolutely perfect!
地球をほら 踏み込む蹄鉄
Look at our horseshoes stamping on the Earth!
ゴール前のキセキ
A miracle right before the finish line,
仕掛ける場所は最終コーナー
The place to make our move is the final corner!
あとは行けるどこまで息を切らしてさあ
From here on, run out of breath
and go as far as we can, come on!
何万と手を叩くオーディエンス
Tens of thousands in the audience clapping their hands,
割れんばかり響く大歓声
A roaring cheer echoing loud enough to split the sky!
ファンファーレが鳴る
The fanfare rings out,
心音が高鳴る
Our heartbeats are racing,
動き出す秒針 夢のゲートが開く
The second hand begins to move,
the gate of dreams swings open!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
走って
Run!
憧れを追い越して
Surpassing our dreams,
次は誰の番だ！？
Whose turn is next?!
さあ目指すはスーパーーー
Come on, our goal is super...
なー！
Yeah!
生きてく
To live...
ハイ！
Hi!
意味なんて
...what does it even mean?
ハイ！
Hi!
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
That's something to think about after pulling ahead!
勝ちたい！
I want to win!
そう、これは本能
Yes, this is instinct!
走りたい！
I want to run!
止まない衝動
An unstoppable urge!
叫びたい！
I want to shout!
勝利の雄叫びよ
Let the victory roar...
轟け！
...echo out!
誰かとバチバチ競うことでしか
Only by fiercely competing with someone
到達し得ない輝かしいゴールライン
can we reach that shining finish line.
Ah どんな
Ah, no matter...
理屈でも言語化できない感情
...what logic, this feeling cannot be put into words.
科学を超えて
Going beyond science,
オカルト超えて
going beyond the occult,
熱い勝負したい！したい！したい！
I want to have a heated match! I do! I do!
どちらが最強か
Which of us is the strongest?
決めようか好敵手
Let's decide it, worthy rival!
速い者が勝つ 何も言い訳はなしさ
The fastest wins, there are no excuses.
「よーいどん！」
"Ready, set, go!"
飛ばして
Fly high,
ハイ！
Hi!
飛ばして
fly high,
ハイ！
Hi!
涙さえ振り切って
and shake off even your tears!
前に足を出すんだ
Keep stepping forward,
悩む暇なんてない
there's no time to hesitate!
答えを
The answer...
ハイ！
Hi!
出すのは
...is something you can find
ハイ！
Hi!
ゴールした後でも遅くない
even after crossing the goal!
Go fight!
抗えぬ本能
Instinct that can't be resisted,
絶対！
absolutely!
譲れない頂上
The summit we can't yield,
騒ぎたい！
I want to make some noise!
王者の雄叫びに
In response to the champion's roar...
続け！
...let's keep going!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
「いくぞー！」
"Here we go!"
どんなことが起こったって
No matter what happens,
レースが止まらないように
so that the race won't stop,
ずっと続いてゆくこの友情
this friendship will continue forever.
憎まれ口をたたいたって保存
Even if we exchange sarcastic remarks,
みんな一列になれば
once we all line up,
Ah てっぺんめがけて
Ah, aiming for the top...
位置についてよーい
...get on your marks... get ready...
走って 走って
Run, run,
走って
run,
ハイ！
Hi!
走って
run,
ハイ！
Hi!
憧れを追い越して
and overtake our aspirations!
次は誰の番だ！？
Who is up next?!
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Now, let's aim to be a superstar!
生きてく
To live...
ハイ！
Hi!
意味なんて
...what does it even mean?
ハイ！
Hi!
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
That's something to think about after pulling ahead!
勝ちたい！
I want to win!
そう、これは本能
Yes, this is instinct!
走りたい！
I want to run!
止まない衝動
An unstoppable urge!
叫びたい！
I want to shout!
勝利の雄叫びよ
Let the victory roar...
轟け！
...echo out!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
ひゃああっ！冷たーい！
Hyah! It's so cold!
バンドして汗かいちゃったからね〜、リフレッシュ、リフレッシュ！
We got sweaty from playing in the band. Refresh, refresh!
ほら、おまるも早く進んでー！
Hey, Omaru, hurry up and get in!
ああああああああああ！地獄シャワー無理〜〜〜！！！
Aaaaaah! The hell shower is impossible!
シャワー浴びて、プールで泳いで遊んだら…きっといいアイデアも出てくるってば！
Once we take a shower and play in the pool... I'm sure we'll come up with some great ideas!
…そう言って、毎回遊び疲れて終わるんだけどね〜〜
...You say that, but every time we just end up exhausted from playing.
でもさ！夏といえばプールでしょ！ここで何かするのもアリじゃない？
But still, summer means the pool! Isn't it a good idea to do something here?
プールでできることといえば……
Speaking of what we can do in a pool...
撮影会！！
A photoshoot!!
ねねたちの水着姿で！
With us in our swimsuits!
お客さんを……悩殺♡
To... captivate our audience.
ダメに決まってるだろ！！会長に怒られるよっ！！
Of course we can't do that! The president will get mad at us!
絶対に盛り上がるのにな〜〜
But it would definitely be a huge hit...
……プールにラミィちゃん沈めて、産地直送ラミィ水……これは売れる！！
...If we submerge Lamy-chan in the pool and sell "Direct from Source Lamy Water"... This will sell!
そこっ！！ラミィから出汁とろうとするな！！ラミィ水は忘れろ！！
Hey! Don't try to make broth out of Lamy! Forget about Lamy Water!
…じゃあ、ライブしとく？プールサイドで！
...Then, how about a live show? On the poolside!
まぁそうなるよね〜。でも夏、プール、歌…最高にマッチしてるっ！
Well, that makes sense. But summer, the pool, and music... They match perfectly!
いいねいいね！あの夏フェスの曲やろうよ〜！水鉄砲とか持って、みんなでびしょびしょになりながら！
Nice, nice! Let's perform that summer festival song! Holding water guns, with everyone getting soaking wet!
え？でもあれってエモい感じの恋愛ソングじゃなかった……？
Eh? But wasn't that an emotional love song...?
それをわたしたちなりに歌い上げるってことよ！
And we're going to sing it in our own style!
フェスにぴったりの選曲だからね！
It's the perfect song choice for a festival!
それじゃあ、終わらない夏にするぞーーー！！！
Alright then, let's make it an endless summer!!!
おーーーー！！！！
Oh!!!
君と夏フェス
[Title: Kimi to Natsu Fes]
まだ照れ臭いあいつとフェスに
Going to a festival with him, who's still acting shy,
行く約束をしたはいいけど
We made a promise to go together, but...
あまりノってたら引かれそう
If I get too into it, I might turn him off.
控えめに楽しむって決めたんだ
So I decided I'd enjoy it in moderation.
でも私の大好きな
But my favorite...
ロックスター 真夏のステージで
rock star on this midsummer stage,
スーツを着たロックスター もう
a rock star wearing a suit... Oh,
我慢できない！
I just can't hold back anymore!
止まらないのは私の汗
What won't stop is my sweat,
それとも君への気持ち？
or is it my feelings for you?
滴り落ちてく恋心
My love is dripping down.
こぼれないようにすくってね
Please scoop it up so it won't spill!
止まらないのは夏への期待
What won't stop is my anticipation for summer.
忘れられない夏になるかも
This might become an unforgettable summer!
夏の日差しで焼け焦げそう
The summer sun feels scorching hot.
すべてがスローモーションになる
Everything feels like it's in slow motion.
他人の汗もどうでもよくて
I don't even care about other people's sweat,
日差しの鬱陶しさも感じない
and I don't even feel the annoying heat of the sun.
でも私の大好きなロックスター
But my favorite rock star,
ラストの曲終わり
at the end of their last song,
ロックスター帰っていく
that rock star leaves the stage.
ライブが終わって我に返って
As the live show ends, I snap back to reality,
それから...
and then...
ずいぶん前のほうに来ちゃってたみたい
It seems we ended up quite close to the front.
さっきまで二人がいた場所 もう違う景色
The spot where we stood moments ago already looks different.
あぁ わたしやっちゃった
Oh, I've really done it now...
本気だったのに
Even though I was completely serious.
うつむく私の隣に君が
As I look down, you're right beside me,
わたしの目を見つめる君
looking straight into my eyes.
時間が止まってるみたい
It feels like time has stopped.
少し笑って君はいう
With a gentle smile, you say...
「新しい君が見れたから 今日は本当に来て良かった」
"I got to see a new side of you, so I'm really glad I came today."
照れ笑いの奥見えちゃいそうで
Feeling like you might see right through my bashful smile,
私は焦って目をそらした
I hurriedly looked away in a panic.
止まらないのは二人の恋だ
What won't stop is the love between the two of us.
今年の夏よ
Oh, summer of this year,
終わらないでよ。
please don't end.
はぁー、遊んだ遊んだ
Whew, we sure played a lot!
もう、くったくた。で、結局なんも決まってないっていう
I'm completely exhausted... And in the end, we didn't decide a thing.
制服、洗濯に出しちゃったし、今日の衣装、いつもの着替えしかないよ〜
I sent my school uniform to the laundry, so we only have our usual outfits for today.
もうこのままの格好で何かやるしかないね〜っ！
In that case, we'll just have to perform in these outfits!
でもさ、やっぱりわたしたちにできることって、歌とダンスかなって思うんだよね
But you know, in the end, I really think our best options are singing and dancing.
うん、変に着飾らずに、いつものわたしたちを見せるのが一番かも
Yeah. Without trying to force anything fancy, showing them our usual selves is probably best.
よっし、じゃあ歌う曲決めようよ！ ねねは、エモい感じがいいな。いつもと違う感じの
Alright! Then let's pick a song to sing! I want something emotional, different from our usual style!
ポルカは、恋愛ソングやってみたいなぁ
I'd really love to do a love song!
ラミィは元気いっぱい、合いの手たっぷりな盛り上がるやつ！
I want something high-energy with lots of call-and-response!
歌詞がグッと心にくる系の曲もいいなぁ
A song with lyrics that touch the heart would be nice, too.
うーん
Hmm...
まあ、みんな好みがバラバラだしね～
Well, everyone's tastes are so different~
でも全部は無理くない？
But isn't doing all of them impossible?
いや、できる！やってみなきゃ始まらないっ！
No, we can do it! We won't know unless we try!
まさか…全部やる気？
Don't tell me... you want to do all of them?
もちろん！どれか1つなんてもったいないでしょ！
Of course! Just picking one would be such a waste!
全部やって良いのがあるのか考えよう！
Let's do all of them and see which one is best!
ちょっとは休憩入れさせてね…
At least let us take a little break...
だったらさ！
In that case!
各自、自分の部屋でやりたい曲をやっていこっ！
How about we each perform the songs we want in our own rooms!
じゃあまずはねねからねっ！！
Then Nene goes first!!
この曲は～～、ねねは違う服でやる！
For this song... Nene's going to wear a different outfit!
わかった！やろうか～
Alright! Let's do it.
今度こそ……これで出し物を決めるぞ〜！
This is it... This will decide our performance!
じゃあ！やりますか！！
Alright! Let's do this!!
ねね～着替え終わった？
Nene, are you done changing?
オッケーッ！それじゃあ、いきま〜〜〜〜すっ！！
Okay! Here... we... go!!
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten by now
夏の木陰に座ったまま
As we sat in the shade of summer
氷菓を口に放り込んで風を待っていた
We popped popsicles in our mouths and waited for the breeze
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten by now
世の中の全部嘘だらけ
That everything in this world is full of lies
本当の価値を二人で
How we said we'd go search
探しに行こうと笑ったこと
For its true value together and laughed
忘れないように
So I won't forget
色褪せないように
So it won't fade away
形に残るものが全てじゃないように
So that physical things aren't everything
言葉をもっと教えて
Teach me more words
夏が来るって教えて
Tell me that summer is coming
僕は描いてる
I am painting...
眼に映ったのは夏の亡霊だ
What's reflected in my eyes is a summer ghost
風にスカートが揺れて
With my skirt swaying in the wind
想い出なんて忘れて
Forget about those memories
浅い呼吸をする
Take a shallow breath
汗を拭って夏めく
Wipe away the sweat as summer begins
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten by now
夏の木陰に座った頃
Back when we sat in the shade of summer
遠くの丘から顔出した
There was a cloud peeking out
雲があったじゃないか
From the distant hill, wasn't there?
君はそれを掴もうとして
You tried to reach out and grab it
馬鹿みたいに空を切った手で
With hands grasping foolishly at the empty air
僕は紙に雲一つを書いて
So I drew a single cloud on paper
笑って握って見せて
And showed it to you with a smile in my fist
忘れないように
So I won't forget
色褪せないように
So it won't fade away
歴史に残るものが全てじゃないから
Because things left in history aren't everything
今だけ顔も失くして
Losing our faces just for now
言葉も全部忘れて
And forgetting all our words
君は笑ってる
You are smiling
夏を待っている僕ら亡霊だ
We are ghosts waiting for summer
心をもっと教えて
Tell me more about your heart
夏の匂いを教えて
Tell me the scent of summer
浅い呼吸をする
Take a shallow breath
忘れないように
So I won't forget
色褪せないように
So it won't fade away
心に響くものが全てじゃないから
Because things that echo in our hearts aren't everything
言葉をもっと教えて
Teach me more words
さよならだって教えて
Even teach me how to say goodbye
今も見るんだよ
I still see them even now...
夏に咲いてる花に亡霊を
The ghosts in the flowers blooming in summer
言葉じゃなくて時間を
Give me time, not words
時間じゃなくて心を
Give me your heart, not time
浅い呼吸をする
Take a shallow breath
汗を拭って夏めく
Wipe away the sweat as summer begins
夏の匂いがする
I smell summer
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten by now
夏の木陰に座ったまま
As we sat in the shade of summer
氷菓を口に放り込んで風を待っていた
Tossed a popsicle in my mouth, waiting for the breeze
土曜日は 会えることが 当たり前になって
Saturdays, meeting you became a given
不安からの あの気持ちが 消えてちょっと寂しいの
The anxious feelings from before faded, making me a bit lonely
一生分のキスの回数 すぐに超えちゃうよ
We'll easily exceed a lifetime's worth of kisses
まだ少し まだもっと
Just a bit more, even more
特別でいたい
I want to feel special
ずっと
Always...
出会ってから付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's keep that feeling we had from when we met to when we dated
わかってるふりなんて 100年後もいらない
I don't need us pretending to understand each other, even in a hundred years
二人の合図が増えたって 大事なこと言おう
Even if we have more secret signs, let's say what matters
夏の日の始まりを
The beginning of a summer day...
季節が変わっても覚えてて
Please remember it even as the seasons change
月曜は あえないなら 次の日はどうって？
"Since we can't meet on Monday, how about the next day?"
繰り返しの 言葉だって それをもっと言ってよね
Even if it's the same words over and over, say them more
一回だけのキスのために すぐに会いに来た
I came to see you right away just for a single kiss
あの時の あの場所は 特別じゃないし
That place back then wasn't anywhere special
ずっと
Always...
出会ってから付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's keep that feeling we had from when we met to when we dated
素気ないふりなんて かっこよくもないよ
Pretending to be indifferent isn't cool at all
間違いないこと増えたって 幸せちょっと違う
Even if we have more certainties, happiness feels a bit different
夏の日の始まりが
The beginning of a summer day...
正しい恋をほら 映してる
Look, it reflects a true love
ずっと
Always...
出会ってから付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's keep that feeling we had from when we met to when we dated
わかってるふりなんて 100年後もいらない
I don't need us pretending to understand each other, even in a hundred years
二人の合図が増えたって 大事なこと言おう
Even if we have more secret signs, let's say what matters
夏の日の始まりを
The beginning of a summer day...
季節が変わっても覚えてて
Please remember it even as the seasons change
ハイ ハイ ハイ
Yes, yes, yes!
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
ねえ 歌うわ
Hey, I will sing!
そうよ あなたに
Yes, for you!
甘えたいけれど 恥ずかしいかもね
I want to spoil you, but it might be embarrassing...
かもね Oi!
...maybe! Oi!
願い事の呪文 ほら
Here is my spell for wishes
ムニャムニャムニャ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Mumble, mumble, mumble... Yes, yes, yes, yes!
ずっとこのまま時が止まらぬかもね
Time might just stand still like this forever
止まらぬかもね
It might not stop...
こういうのが恋なの？ ドキドキドきーん
Is this what love is? Pounding, pounding!
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
しかもね かもね
And besides, maybe...
スキスキスキ
I love, love, love you!
昨日よりも かもね
Even more than yesterday, maybe...
ハイハイハイ！ ハイハイハイハイ！
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
かもね かもね
Maybe... maybe...
ハイハイハイ！ ハイハイハイハイ！
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
ねえ 歌って
Hey, sing for me!
そうよ あなたも
Yes, you too!
乙女の気持ちが伝わるといいな いいな
I hope this girl's feelings reach you... I hope so!
のどから出そうなくらい もう ラブラブラブ
It's almost bursting out of my throat, so much love, love, love!
ずっとこのまま あなた 素敵がいいな いいな
I want to stay like this forever, you being wonderful is so nice!
こういうのははじめて ドキドキドきーん
This is my first time feeling like this, pounding, pounding!
ああ いいな いいな
Ah, it's so nice!
スキスキスキ
I love, love, love you!
さっきよりも いいな いいな
Even more than a moment ago, it's so nice!
ハイハイハイ！ ハイハイハイハイ！
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
神様のヒマ潰し
[Song: God's Killing Time]
いつだって新しいことに
You are always captivated by new things,
君は心奪われるから
because they steal your heart away.
クルクルと変わる
Spinning and changing,
お天気 謎だらけ
like the weather, you are full of mysteries.
いつだってTVをつけても
No matter when I turn on the TV,
知りたいことは1つもないよ
there isn't a single thing I want to know.
似たようなウワサ
It's nothing but similar rumors,
ばかり 謎がない
there's no mystery at all.
手に入れたいんだ 君の心の地図
I want to get my hands on the map to your heart.
Ah 探し当てたい 宝物のありか
Ah, I want to find the location of the treasure.
その心の奥を掴んで 揺さぶるものは何？
What is it that grabs the depths of your heart and shakes it?
考えてるだけで 日が暮れる
Just thinking about it makes the day end.
苦しくて 切なくて 楽しくて 日が暮れる
Through pain, sadness, and joy, the day ends.
勘ぐってありえない想像
Making wild, impossible guesses...
へこんだかと思えば笑ったり
Feeling down one moment and laughing the next.
あたしはあたしで
I am who I am,
相当 謎だらけ
and I'm quite full of mysteries myself.
ハマってしまったら 恋は迷路
Once you fall into it, love is a maze.
Ah 角を曲がれば 行き止まりばかり
Ah, turn a corner, and it's nothing but dead ends.
物語の鍵を握って 遊んでいるのは誰？
Who is the one holding the key to the story and playing around?
ずいぶん悪趣味なヒマ潰し
It's quite a bad-taste way of killing time...
退屈を もてあそぶ 神様のヒマ潰し
Toying with boredom, it's God's way of killing time.
このところの
Lately...
不安な夜は
on uneasy nights,
胸の奥の奥
deep, deep inside my chest,
チリチリと鳴き通す
it keeps buzzing restlessly.
Ah
会えない理由はわかってるのに
even though I know the reason we can't meet.
物語の鍵を握って遊んでいるのは誰？
Who is the one holding the key to the story and playing around?
ずいぶん悪趣味なヒマ潰し
A rather bad-tasted way to kill time.
その心の奥を掴んで揺さぶるものは何？
What is it that grabs and shakes the depths of that heart?
考えてるだけで日が暮れる
Just thinking about it makes the day end...
苦しくて切なくて
Painfully, sadly,
楽しくて日が暮れる
joyfully, the day ends.
苦しくて切なくて
Painfully, sadly,
この恋に明け暮れる
spending all my time in this love.
つっ……疲れた〜〜！！
I'm... so tired!
さすがに... 全員曲連続は応えたね...
Performing all the group songs in a row was definitely tough...
でもでも！どの曲もサイコーだった〜〜！
But still, every song was the absolute best!
うん... でも、"わたし達らしさ"があるかって言われると... ちょっと悩むな〜
Yeah... But if you ask if they felt uniquely like us, I'm a bit unsure.
う〜〜ん
Hmm...
まもなく、学寮祭が始まります
The Dormitory Festival will begin shortly.
関係する生徒の皆さんは、速やかに準備をお願いします
All students involved, please get ready immediately.
やっ、やば〜い！！もう始まっちゃうってば〜〜！
Oh, no! It's already starting!
え〜〜お腹空いた〜〜ちょっと購買行ってくるねっ！！
Ugh, I'm so hungry! I'm going to the school store real quick!
じゃ、わたしも行く〜〜
Then I'll go too.
ラミィも行く〜〜！
Lamy's coming too!
えぇ〜〜！？ちょっと〜！？
Wait, what?! Hey!
パン残ってるかな〜〜
I wonder if there's any bread left...
……ん？ あれって……なんだ？
Hm? What is... that over there?
こ、これは！
Th-this is...!
もしかして……！
Could it be...!
もしかしなくても！
Even without a doubt!
間違いないっ！！！
There's no mistake about it!
ネポラボ アニバーサリーパレード！！！
NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade!
ネポラボ5周年グッズがこんなところに！！！
The NePoLaBo 5th Anniversary Merch is in a place like this?!
きっと今日の配信終わりに出るやつだ。
This must be the stuff that goes on sale after today's stream.
気になる〜〜！
I'm so curious!
これは順番に見ていくしかないでしょう！
We have no choice but to look through them one by one!
まずは、プレミアムアクリル色紙！
First up is the Premium Acrylic Art Board!
今回のグッズのテーマが、花鳥風月！
The theme for this merch line is Kachou Fuugetsu!
七原しえさんが描いてくれました！
It was illustrated by Shie Nanahara!
ねねたちの和服姿、綺麗でしょ〜？
Aren't we beautiful in our Japanese attire?
アクリル色紙には、ねねたちの複製サインとロゴが入ってます。
The acrylic board features our printed signatures and the logo.
アクリルの足もついてるから、机に飾っておくこともできるよ！
It comes with acrylic stands so you can display it on your desk!
めっちゃ可愛いので、ぜひ！
It's super cute, so please check it out!
次っ！
Next!
続いては、hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME オフィシャルホカスリーブ アニバーサリーパレード ネポラボバージョン！
Next up is the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME Official Foil Sleeve: Anniversary Parade NePoLaBo Version!
もちろん、ホロカが入るスリーブです！
Naturally, these sleeves fit your Holoka cards!
1パック60枚入ってるから、これでネポラボデッキを作り上げてください！
One pack contains 60 sleeves, so use them to build your NePoLaBo deck!
いや、もう最近はね、ネポラボ全員出てますから、
Seriously, with all of NePoLaBo now in the game,
もうこれでね、お前のオリジナルのデッキ構築をして、優勝していくんだ！
you can build your own original deck and seize victory!
さあ、お前ならできる！やるしかない！
Go on, you can do it! You've got this!
見ているお前ら、ネポラボリスナー！お前ら頑張ってくれ！！
All you NePoLaBo fans watching, give it your absolute best!!
次っ！
Next!
続いては、アクリルスタンド！
Next up is the Acrylic Stands!
プレミアムアクリル色紙とは別表情をした、ラミィたちのアクリルスタンドです。
These feature different expressions than the art board!
花鳥風月で、花・春が桃鈴ねね、
For Kachou Fuugetsu: 'Flower/Spring' is Momosuzu Nene,
鳥・秋が獅白ぼたん、
'Bird/Autumn' is Shishiro Botan,
風・夏が尾丸ポルカ、
'Wind/Summer' is Omaru Polka,
月・冬が雪花ラミィとなっています。
and 'Moon/Winter' is Yukihana Lamy.
では、次！
And next!
最後は、記念メダル！
Lastly is the Memorial Medal!
専用のケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルです。
This medal comes with a special case and a drawstring pouch.
それぞれタレントカラーと名前が入っていて、期生ごとにデザインが違うので、
Each features our colors and names, and since the designs differ by member,
コレクションアイテムとしてぜひ揃えてみてください。
they are perfect collector's items. Try gathering them all!
以上、ネポラボ アニバーサリーパレードのグッズでした！
And that's all for the NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade merch!
やったー！いぇーい！
Yeah! We did it!
それでは、これより、学寮祭を開始いたします。
And now, we will begin the Dormitory Festival.
ご来場の皆様、どうぞ、最後までお楽しみください。
To all visitors, please enjoy it until the very end.
やばい！学寮祭始まるって！
Oh no! The festival is starting!
ねねたちも行かなきゃ！
We have to go too!
結局、何も買えなかったんだけど！
In the end, we didn't get to buy anything!
仕方ない、戻って学寮祭の話をしますか…
We have no choice. Let's go back and talk about the Dormitory Festival...
で？これは…何をしているの？
So? What... are we doing here?
ねねたちには、歌とダンスしかないっ！
We only have our singing and dancing!
ならばギリギリまで、全力で練習するしかないでしょー！
So we have no choice but to practice with all our might until the very last second!
もうお客さん入っているけどね。
But the audience is already in, you know?
あぁっ、もうやるしかないっ！
Ah, we just have to do it!
でもさ、肝心の「何やるか」決めてないのでは？
But wait... haven't we decided on the crucial part, \"what\" we're actually going to do?
うーん…
Hmm...
でもさ、お客さんたちが見たいのって…
But you know, what the audience wants to see...
やっぱり「わたしちらしさ」だよね。
...is surely \"our unique style,\" right?
それなら、オリ曲じゃない？
If so, shouldn't it be our original songs?
じゃあ、全部やろっ！
Then let's do them all!
また〜〜〜！？
Again!?
1つだけじゃダメダメっ！
Just one is not enough!
衣装もぜーんぶ着替えて、たくさん歌おうよ！
Let's change into all our outfits and sing a ton of songs!
メドレーってこと！？いいじゃんそれ！
You mean a medley!? That sounds great!
おぉ、いいかも！
Oh, that might be good!
で、順番はどうするの？
So, what about the order?
そんなん、パッションでどうにかなるなるっ！
We can figure that out with pure passion!
こりゃ大変なことになりそうですね…
This is going to turn into quite a disaster...
うーん…
Hmm...
ししろん、どうしたの？
Shishiron, what's wrong?
いや、何か忘れている気がするんだけど…思い出せない…
Well, I feel like we're forgetting something... but I can't recall what.
大丈夫大丈夫っ！
It'll be fine, it'll be fine!
これを歌えば学寮祭は、ねねたちのものっ！
Once we sing this, the Dormitory Festival will be ours!
よっしゃ、いくぞー！
Alright, let's go!
「わたしちらしさ」、見せるよ！
We'll show them \"our unique style\"!
うん、とりあえずやるだけやろう。せーのっ！
Yeah, let's just do our best for now. One, two, three!
ねぽらぼメドレー！
Nepolabo Medley!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands all the way across the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
Shining light upon our future
始めようか さあ Diving
Shall we begin? Come on, let's dive in
待ってても意味ない Timing
There's no point in waiting for the perfect timing
でもたまに立ち止まって Thinking thinking
But sometimes, take a pause and keep thinking, thinking
変えてみせる Change
I'll show you I can change
踏み出すのさ Stepping
Take that step forward
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ My dream
I'll seize my sparkling dream
叶う日まで Story 繋ぐから
I'll keep connecting the story until the day it comes true
だって君に ずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching me forever
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands all the way across the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら 一緒に Everybody
Come on, everybody, let's do it together
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Clap your hands all the way across the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it resonates
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
Shining light upon our future
Hyper Jumpin' Now
子どもくらいはしゃぐ方がおトクでしょ
It's better to run around wildly like a kid, right?
低気圧から這い上がっていくテンション
Our tension is rising up from low atmospheric pressure
このままスピード加速して
Just accelerating the speed like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
What lies at the end of our destination?
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
These unstoppable feelings are gaining momentum
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さぁ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Now, hyper jumpin', let's leap and bound
ハイになって灰になるまで ダンシング Shake it up
Let's get high until we burn to ash, dancing, shake it up
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin' all the way across the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Woh... Woh...
ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to feel my heart thumping, gimme gimme gimme love
Woh... Woh...
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
disはNo No
Disliking is a no-no
好きなら More More More
If you like us, give us more, more, more
邪魔するノイズは
The noise that gets in our way
撃ち消せ Bang Bang Bang
Shoot it down! Bang, bang, bang!
遊びたいだけ
We just want to play
アンチは無視して
Ignore the haters
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴っ飛ばせ
Kick it away
Kick it!!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
一歩目がすでに異空間
My first step is already in a different space
キラリ 渦に巻き込まれた？
Was I sucked into a sparkling vortex?
違うよ 出会いたくって
No, it's because I wanted to meet you
ほら みんなここにいる
Look, everyone is right here
夢のようで… だけどね
It's like a dream... but you know
ファンタジーじゃない予感
I have a feeling it's not a fantasy
流星群 負けないよう
Like a meteor shower, so we won't lose
光放って！
Emit our light!
どんな憧れも飛び越えて
Leaping over any kind of yearning
銀河のまん中が行進しよう
Let's march right through the middle of the galaxy
キラめきのシンフォニーさ
It's a sparkling symphony
足跡だって星になる
Even our footprints will turn into stars
1, 2, 3... Yeah!
奇跡散りばめ
Sprinkling miracles
1, 2, 3... Yeah!
何万光年を
Tens of thousands of light-years
1, 2, 3... Yeah!
旅してゆく季節が今
The season of our travels is now
始まったんだよきっと
Beginning, for sure!
せーの！ ワンダフルツアー！
Ready, set, go! Wonderful Tour!
ワンダフルツアー！
Wonderful Tour!
君に届け 星のメロディー
May the melody of the stars reach you
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing all our feelings tightly, so tightly
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
This harmony I play with you
これからもずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever from now on
ねえねえ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey, hey, come a little closer
回り始めた世界で踊らない？終わらない
Won't you dance in this spinning world? It won't end
わくわく 魔法かけたら
Once we cast a thrilling magic spell
ドキドキはSyncしてほら Party Time 止まらない
Our heartbeats sync up, look, it's Party Time, it won't stop
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
Make a wish upon them
Twinkle Twinkle 夜空で歌いましょう
Twinkle Twinkle, let's sing in the night sky
君に響け 星のメロディー
May the melody of the stars resound to you
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
This harmony I play with you
これからもずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever from now on
Twinkle 4 You
君に響け 星のメロディー
May the melody of the stars resound to you
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と繋がっているこの宇宙に
In this sky where I am connected with you
宝石を散りばめよう
Let's sprinkle gemstones
君に届け 星のメロディー
May the melody of the stars reach you
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing all our feelings tightly, so tightly
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
This harmony I play with you
これからもずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever from now on
La La La...
やっぱ、ねぽらぼだな〜！！
As expected, it has to be NePoLaBo!!
これで学園祭は大成功〜！！
With this, the school festival is a huge success!!
う〜ん……
Hmm...
え、ししろん？どうしたの？
Eh, Shishiron? What's wrong?
いやさ……確かに良かったんだけど……なんかこう……何かを忘れてる気がするんだよね
Well... it was definitely great, but...
somehow... I feel like we forgot something.
なぁに言ってんの！このメドレーで完璧だってば！
What are you talking about!
With this medley, it was perfect!
そうだよ〜！これでみ〜んな、ひとつになってハッピー！！
That's right! With this, everyone became one
and is happy!!
来てくれた人たちも、きっとラミィたちの”声”を聴いて、喜んでくれたよ！
I'm sure the people who came were happy
to hear our voices too!
ひとつ……声……あっ！！！
One... voice... Ah!!!
私たち、新曲作ってたじゃん！！！
We had made a new song, didn't we?!
あっ……
Ah...
わすれてたぁーーーー！！！
We totally forgot about it!!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのにっ！！
Even though we practiced so much for it!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのにっ！
We practiced so hard!
作ったのはいいけど……「出すタイミングどうしよう」って言ってたら、
Making it was fine, but while we were wondering when to present it...
完全に忘れてた……
...we completely forgot.
出すタイミング絶対にここだったなー
The perfect timing to show it was definitely here...
もうステージ真っ暗だしーーー！
The stage is already pitch black!
お客さん……まだいてくれてる、かな……
Our fans... I wonder if they're still there...
大丈夫！今なら、まだ……ギリギリ間に合う！
It's okay! If it's now, we can still make it in the nick of time!
ねえ！そこの君！まだ……見てくれてるよね？
Hey! You over there! You're still watching, right?
ねねたちの、新しい曲ーー聞いてくれる？
Will you listen... to our new song?
うん、うん……きっと、聞いてくれるって信じてる！
Yeah, yeah... I'm sure they will. I believe in them!
最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていこうね！
Let's fire up together until the very end!
それではーー改めて……んん……聞いてください、ねぽらぼの新曲です！
Well then, once again... *cough* Please listen to Neporabo's new song!
この先、みんなとなら、どこまでも行けると願ってーー歌います。
Hoping that we can go anywhere if we're with everyone in the future—we will sing.
5周年ーーその先の未来もずっと一緒に見守り……歩んでください
Our 5th anniversary—please continue to watch over us and walk with us into the future.
1人じゃ辿り着けない場所へ……みんなでーー
To a place we couldn't reach alone... together with everyone—
ひとつになる声
Our voices becoming one!
暗闇の中で 見つけた声
The voice I found in the darkness,
そのしるべを 辿りながら
as I trace that guidepost...
僕らは 走るよ
...we will run.
ひとりぼっちだった日
The day I was all alone,
先見えなかった日
the days when I couldn't see ahead.
だけど君と出会えて
But meeting you,
そっと 扉を開けた
gently opened the door.
手のひらの中に また1を足して
Adding one more inside our palms,
何度も 奇跡を叶えよう
let's make miracles happen over and over again.
澄み渡る空の彼方
Beyond the clear blue sky,
太陽と踊る 羽になる
becoming wings that dance with the sun.
情熱が突き動かす
Passion drives us forward,
僕らの明日を 照らして
illuminating our tomorrow.
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは
We, who chase the same dream,
強く心を結んで
tightly tie our hearts together.
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
Because we can go anywhere in the ends of the earth.
これからまた続いてく道
The path that continues from here on,
1人じゃ辿り着けない
we can't reach alone.
だから この背中預けるよ
So, I will entrust my back to you.
信じている 君の手を
I believe in your hand,
僕らの未来を
our future...
みんなの声を
...everyone's voices.
君らしいって思う
I think, 'That's so you.'
その積み重ねが
That accumulation of moments
なぜか嬉しくなるの
somehow makes me happy.
きっと これからもそう
I'm sure it'll always be like this.
手のひらの中の 大切な日々が
The precious days inside our palms
沢山の光を奏でて
will play lots of light,
君と笑った
as we laughed with you.
始まりの時の願い
Our wish from when it first began,
今もほら輝いてる
is still shining now, you see.
未来まで連れてゆこう
Let's take it with us to the future!
暗闇を抜けた先に
Beyond the darkness,
みんなの笑顔 見つけた
I found everyone's smiles.
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは
We, who chase the same dream,
強く心を結んで
tightly tie our hearts together.
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
Because we can go anywhere in the ends of the earth.
これからまた続いてく道
The path that continues from here on,
1人じゃ辿り着けない
we can't reach alone.
だから この背中預けるよ
So, I will entrust my back to you.
信じている 君の手を
I believe in your hand,
僕らの未来を
our future...
みんなの声を ひとつに
...everyone's voices, becoming one.
ひとつに
As one...
みんなの声を
Let's combine...
重ねて
...our voices together.
みんなの声を
Let's bring everyone's voices...
ひとつに
...together as one.
みんなの声を
Let's combine...
重ねて
...our voices together.
みんなの声を
Let's bring everyone's voices...
ひとつに
...together as one.
心合わせて
With our hearts aligned...
重ねて
...and overlapping,
僕らは願う
...we make our wish.
ひとつに
Together as one...
光の中で
...inside this bright light,
重ねて
...overlapping...
ひとつになる声
...voices becoming one!